http://www.privacyanywhere.com/privacy/

Download PestBlock Spyware Removal!Buy best Privacy Guard. Your privacy will be strongly protected with Privacy Guard named as Evidence Sweeper! Download Spyware Removal Software!
Spyware Removal Software for Free!The Best Spyware Removal Software!
Privacy Defender Software Download!Try our Privacy Defender Software!
Home
Products
Downloads
Support
Contacts
Affiliates/Resellers
Company
Online Store
Home /
Privacy Statement
At PrivacyAnywhere Software, your security and privacy is of the utmost importance to us. We take the following steps to protect your personal information:
PERSONAL INFORMATION
PrivacyAnywhere Software collects basic contact information when you subscribe to newsletter or fill in a contact form. This information will be used for administrative and identification purposes only and will not be shared with our partners or third parties. Personal information is stored on PrivacyAnywhere Software computers and is only accessed by authorized PrivacyAnywhere Software personnel.
GENERAL INFORMATION
PrivacyAnywhere Software also collects general demographic information about visitors to our site. The information we collect creates a broad picture of our population rather than focusing on any one individual. This information is used to continually refine our products and to identify the most popular areas of our site.
ENCRYPTED CREDIT CARD PURCHASES
If you use a credit card to purchase a PrivacyAnywhere Software product, the credit card number is encrypted as it passes over the Internet. Your credit card number is not kept or recorded by PrivacyAnywhere Software or our computers - it is simply passed through to the credit card company to purchase the course. In this respect, buying a course from PrivacyAnywhere Software is similar to a credit card purchase at any store. Neither PrivacyAnywhere Software nor the store keeps your credit card number on file.
More than anything, PrivacyAnywhere Software tries to treat its customers as each one of us would like to be treated. We value our privacy and we value yours, too. It is our goal to make your experience with PrivacyAnywhere Software a safe and positive experience.
For more information on PrivacyAnywhere Software's privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at: privacy@privacyanywhere.com
News for Jul 10, 2015
New Version!
PestBlock version 4.1. Many new featured, bugfixes. Download new version today! Learn More...
Download Demo Version
Buy Now!
Buy Online
Online Store
Discount Pricing
Spyware Research
Browse our Spyware Research Center.
Spyware Research
Free Newsletter
Sign up for our free product newsletter today and get informed about new updates and releases by email. You will also receive the latest discounts and offers for our products!
Click Here to Sign Up
Home
Products
Downloads
Support
Contacts
Affiliates/Resellers
Company
© 2007 PrivacyAnywhere Software, LLC. All rights reserved. Privacy Statement | Terms of Use | www.pestblock.com
